(ﾅﾚｰｼｮﾝ)
＜王国を救うため 伝説の逆賊➡
Elizabeth, the third princess of the Liones Kingdom,
七つの大罪を捜す リオネス王国
第三王女エリザベスは➡
presses onward with her search for the
legendary Seven in order to save the kingdom.
Together with the Dragon's Sin of Wrath, Meliodas, her journey continues.
憤怒の罪 憤怒の罪の
メリオダスと共に 旅を続ける＞
＜白夢の森で出会った
巨人族の少女は➡
In the Forest of White Dreams, they met a giant girl,
二人目の七つの大罪 嫉妬の罪
嫉妬の罪のディアンヌであった＞
the second member of the Seven, the Serpent's Sin of Envy, Diane.
Just as she joined the team,
＜彼女が仲間に加わったやさき➡
メリオダスを追い
聖騎士ギルサンダーが現れた＞
the Holy Knight Gilthunder who was chasing Meliodas arrived.
＜接戦の末
ギルサンダーの手によって➡
As the battle was coming to a close,
メリオダスは
倒されてしまったかに見えた＞
the demise of Meliodas appeared imminent.
＜ だが…＞
However...
Thanks, Li'l Gil!
(ﾒﾘｵﾀﾞｽ)サンキュー！ ギル坊｡
The Baste Dungeon and the City of the Dead, right?
バステ監獄と死者の都な｡
どっちか当たってみるよ｡
Guess I'll pay 'em a visit.
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)なるほど｡
仲間の居場所を聞き出すために➡
I see...
You let yourself come to harm in order to find out where your allies are.
私の剣を あえて受けた… と｡
続きは また今度… な｡
We'll continue this some other time, okay?
You wish!
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)ほざけ｡
さらばだ｡
またな｡
Farewell.
See ya.
Captain said "some other time," didn't he?
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)
団長が またなって言ったんだ｡
Unhand me!
放せ！ んんっ！
Didn't I tell you a long time ago that
"shocking" men aren't popular with girls?
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)ピリピリする男は
女の子にモテないって➡
僕が昔 教えたろ！
サンキュー ディアンヌ｡
Thanks, Diane.
Looks like you'll need a new one of those.
それ
ダメになっちゃったな｡
＜ これは いまだ
人と 人ならざるものの世界が➡
This is a tale of humans and beings from other worlds.
分かたれてはいなかった
古の物語＞
It is a story of ancient times.
＜国を守る聖騎士たちは
絶大なる魔力を有し➡
The Holy Knights who protected this country
wielded immensely powerful magic.
They were both feared and revered.
恐れ 敬われた＞
＜ だが その中で 国を裏切り➡
However,
a faction arose who betrayed their country and turned their blades against the remaining Knights.
全聖騎士を
敵に回した者たちがいた＞
＜人々は
彼らを 七つの大罪と呼んだ＞
To the masses, they were known as the "Seven Deadly Sins."
I'll shout out a love that doesn't cease to resound
nariyamanu ai o sakebu yo
I continue to take everything in my arms
subete o daite koko ni irun da
For that's where our light lies
hikari wa soko ni aru yo
I run through my unwavering thoughts
yuzurenai omoi o kakete
I'll be the one to live on the edge of my hopes
kibou no hate o boku wa ikiru yo
A dream connects me to you
yume ni tsunaida kimi to
A beginning will someday be born from our own hands
hajimari o itsuka bokura no te de umidasun da yo
And with how kind you are, I'm sure your voice will be able to change the world
yasashii kimi no koe mo kitto sekai o kaerareru
Since people can't totally stand up all on their own,
dare mo hitori kiri ja tachiagare yashinai kara
we'll reach out our hands to one another
tagai ni te o nobashite
and head for a tomorrow that surpasses all limits
kagiri no koeta ashita e
I'll shout out a love that doesn't cease to resound
nariyamanu ai o sakebu yo
As we begin to butt heads and get to know one another better,
butsukariatte wakariaun da
we'll create a path of light.
hikari o tsukuridasu yo
With unyielding emotions in tow,
akiramenu omoi o kakete
I'll be the one to live on the edge of my hopes
kibou no hate o boku wa ikiru yo
A dream connects me with you
yume ni tsunai da kimi to
≫パカパカ パカパカ…(足音)
(ﾎｰｸ)おうっ こら～！
Hey, you! You've got a lot of nerve messing with me! You bastard pig!
さっきは
よくも やってくれやがったな➡
この豚野郎が！
今度は 俺のターンだぜ｡
It's my turn now!
プゴッ！ プガッ！
(ｴﾘｻﾞﾍﾞｽ)二人とも ご無事ですか!?
Are you two all right?
おう｡
あら!? 豚野郎は？
Yup.
Huh? Where'd that bastard pig go?
豚は お前だろ｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)いい匂～い｡
You're the pig, aren't you?
And he smells delicious!
メリオダス様 その傷は？
ああ～➡
Lord Meliodas, you're wounded!
Oh, it's no big deal.
大したことねぇって｡
だって 血が こんなに！
But you're bleeding so much!
D-Don't get so touchy-feely with Captain!
あ… あんまり
団長に ベタベタしないでよ｡
But—
でも…｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)団長のそばにいるのは➡
It's my job to look after Captain, okay?
僕の役目なんだからね｡
手当てするなら 僕がやる！
If anyone's gonna help him, it'll be me.
Hey, I'm injured too! He really did a number on me!
俺だって あいつに
ケツ 思いっ切り蹴られたんだぜ！
Here?
ここか？
そこは ｽﾍﾟｱﾘﾌﾞ｡
That's my spare rib...
Here?
ここか？
そこは 肩ロース｡ って わざとか！
That's my shoulder roa—
You're doing this on purpose, aren't you!?
Hawk, let's cool your back down a bit.
ホークちゃん あとで
お尻のお肉 冷やしましょう｡
うわぁ～ん！
心配してくれるのは➡
Elizabeth is the only one who cares about me!
エリザベスちゃんだけだ｡
んん～…｡
(村人)神よ
どうか 王国に連れ去られた➡
O God,
please bring back to us the young men of
the village who were taken by the kingdom.
村の若者たちを お返しください｡
どうか 聖騎士たちに
天罰を与えたまえ｡
Please bring divine retribution to the Holy Knights.
≪カァー！(ｶﾗｽの鳴き声)
ん？
ピシャーン！
Divine... retribution...
天… 罰を…｡
ごふっ…｡
(村人)誰か… 助け…｡
Someone... help me...
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)まあいい｡
Oh well.
Episode 4
A Young Girl's Dream
Ah, that's the spot!
ああ～ そこ そこ｡ 効く～｡
That damn Holy Knight.
ったく 聖騎士の野郎
今度会ったら ただじゃおかねぇ｡
I won't go easy on him next time!
あっ エリザベスちゃんの
知り合いなんだっけ？
So, Elizabeth, you knew that guy?
ええ｡ ギルサンダーは もともと➡
Yes...
Lord Gilthunder was originally my sister Margaret's escort.
マーガレットお姉様の護衛役で➡
He treated me affectionately, like I was his own sister.
私のことも 実の妹のように
かわいがってくれた➡
兄のような人です｡
Even after his father, the Great Holy Knight, passed away, he continued his loyal service.
当時 聖騎士長だったお父上が
亡くなられてからも➡
よく仕えてくれました｡ なのに…｡
And yet...
はっ！
まさか お父様を捕らえたのも…｡
Could he be related to what happened to Father?
What's wrong, Elizabeth?
どうした？ エリザベスちゃん｡
We can never return to that time, can we?
もう
あのころには戻れないのですね｡
So the Fox's Sin of Greed, Ban, was thrown into a dungeon,
強欲の罪 バンは
監獄に ぶち込まれて➡
while the Grizzly's Sin of Sloth, King, is dead and buried...
怠惰の罪 キングは
死んで墓の中か｡
What do you think?
お前 どう思う？
どうでも～｡
I don't care...
僕 団長以外の男に興味ないし｡
I have no interest in men other than Captain.
But enough about that.
そんなことよりさ
僕ってば この１０年に➡
I've become such a fine
woman over these ten years!
こんないい女に
なってたんだ～｡
That's just a sketch, y'know.
その手配書 想像だから｡
It's decided!
よし 決めた！
んん～ 乗ってていいのに｡
You could've kept riding on me...
Let's go pick up Ban at the Baste Dungeon first!
まずは バンを拾いに
バステ監獄に行くぞ｡
おお～！
(ﾎｰｸﾏﾏ)ブゴ～ッ！
Why the Baste Dungeon first?
バステ監獄にした理由は？
近いから｡
安易だな｡
It's closer.
That's the only reason?
わ… 私は反対です｡
I-I disagree!
ん？
今は メリオダス様の➡
Shouldn't we treat your wounds before we go to the dungeon?
傷の手当てが
優先ではないでしょうか｡
If you have to fight another Holy Knight with your body in that condition...
そんな体で また
聖騎士と戦うことになったら…｡
Maybe this'll help.
こうすれば治るかも｡
ほ… 本当ですか？
R-Really?
うそですよ！
んん～…｡
Obviously not!
エリザベス｡
あっ｡
Elizabeth...
It's just a few scratches.
心配すんな なんともねぇから｡
No need to worry.
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)んん～…｡
少し寝りゃ すぐ治る｡ おやすみ｡
I'll be fine with a little rest.
G'night.
I figured he would've asked you to sleep with him or something.
あいつのことだから 添い寝でも➡
要求するかと思ったぜ｡
ちょっと 様子見てきます｡
I'm going to check on him.
Sleep with him, you mean?
添い寝か？
≫ガチャ
コン コン コン
メリオダス様➡
Lord Meliodas.
お着替え お一人で大丈夫ですか？
Are you okay changing your clothes by yourself?
メリオダス… 様…｡
Lord...
Meliodas...
Baste Dungeon
A report from the Royal Palace.
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)王宮より報告です｡➡
白夢の森で
七つの大罪二名が確認されました｡
We've confirmed the presence of two Sins at the Forest of White Dreams.
おそらく
あの男を奪いに来るかと｡
I fear that they'll be coming here in search of a certain someone.
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)
あら～ やっと来るのぉ？➡
Oh?
They're finally coming?
Little Sins.
七つの大罪ちゃん｡
<Weird Fangs>
Holy Knight Fresia
Whether he comes straight here or stops by the neighboring town first,
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)直接 乗り込んでくるか
近辺の町に寄るか…➡
いずれにせよ
何か仕込んでおきましょう｡
I suppose we should be ready to welcome him.
<Weird Fangs>
Holy Knight Golgius
Oh come now, Golgius.
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)ああ～ もう ゴルギウス｡
嫌ぁ～なとこに置くわね｡
What an unpleasant move!
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)
イヒヒ… フリージアの番ですよ｡
It's your turn, Fresia.
Um...
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)あの…｡
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)心配いらないわよ➡
No need to worry, Jericho.
ジェリコちゃん｡ この監獄はね➡
You see, this dungeon
来るべき戦いに備えて造られた
実験的な砦よ｡➡
was built in preparation for battles to come. An experimental fort, you could say.
七つの大罪ごときが そう簡単に
攻略できる所じゃないわ｡
Even for the Seven Deadly Sins,
it won't be easy to conquer this place.
That's true.
(ﾙｲﾝ)そう｡ それに
わしら｢不気味な牙｣がいる｡
Don't forget that we Weird Fangs are here as well.
<Weird Fangs>
Holy Knight Ruin
O-Of course not, Lord Ruin.
も… もちろんです ルイン様｡
(ｼﾞｭﾄﾞ)しかし➡
However,
ヤツらは来るのか？ 本当に｡
I wonder if they'll really come.
<Weird Fangs>
Holy Knight Jude
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)ドゥフフフ！ 確かに➡
Good point.
There's no way anyone would take such a huge risk just to save him.
そこまでの危険を冒してまで
救う価値が➡
彼にあるとは思えないわね｡➡
５年前
私たちに捕らえられてから➡
Since we captured him five years ago, he hasn't basked in the sun,
ずっと 日の光を浴びることなく➡
nor has he moved an inch or
been allowed to speak a word.
動くことも口を利くことも
許されず➡
He hasn't been fed anything worth eating, either.
食事も
ろくに与えられることもなく➡
He's just going to be tortured until the day he dies.
ただただ
死ぬまで 拷問を受け続けてる｡
Although he was a member of the Seven,
I don't know why they'd bother saving him.
(ﾙｲﾝ)仲間に加えたところで
数合わせにもならんな｡
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)
強欲の罪と呼ばれた伝説が➡
To think he was the legendary Fox's Sin of Greed...
哀れなものですねぇ｡
How pitiful.
(牢番)鼻歌？ どこからだ？
That sound...
Where's it coming from?
Approximately 8 Miles Northeast of Baste Dungeon
Dalmary Town
≫ドスン ドスン ドスン…
あっ ねえ この町に…｡
Hey, townspeople!
(町人)きゃあ～！
(町人)巨人族だ～！
It's a giant!
Whoa, you're huge!
でっかい ねえちゃん！
Wait!
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)待って！
お医者さんが どこにいるか➡
I just want to know where the doctors are!
知りたいだけだよ！
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)団長…｡
Captain...
言わんこっちゃない！
I told you so!
Hawk and I will look for a doctor in the village.
あの… お医者様は
私とホークちゃんで探しますから➡
ディアンヌ様は…｡
団長は 僕が助けるんだ！
Diane, can you—
I'll be the one to save Captain!
B-But—
で… でも…｡
お前じゃ みんな びっくりして➡
You're scaring everyone away!
逃げちまうんだよ！
I get it.
分かった｡
ここにいるから探してきてよ｡
Go start looking. I'll wait here.
Y-Yes!
は… はい｡
おとなしくしてろよ｡
Be good and wait for us!
はぁ はぁ はぁ…｡
ドンドコドコドコ ドンドコ…｡
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)ドゥフフフ…｡➡
I've found them!
発見したわよ～｡➡
ゴルギウスの予想どおり｡
Just as Golgius anticipated.
(ｼﾞｭﾄﾞ)行くのか？ フリージア｡
Are you going, Fresia?
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)
ええ｡ この私が 先手を打ち➡
Yes.
I'm going to deliver the first
strike and put an end to him.
ついでに
ピリオドも打ってあげちゃう｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)団長…｡
Captain...
This is a medicine I've prepared myself.
(ﾀﾞﾅ)私の調合した特別製の薬だ｡➡
これで ずっと楽になるよ｡
It'll make him at peace.
Thank you very much, Dr. Dana.
ありがとうございます ダナ先生｡
Honestly, I'm amazed he's still alive.
(ﾀﾞﾅ)正直
生きてるのが不思議なくらいだ｡➡
The wound from the sword is deep,
and he's got a burn as if he was struck by lightning.
相当深い刀傷に
雷に打たれたかのような火傷｡➡
どうして こんな子供が…｡
Why would a kid like this...
私のせいですね｡
This is my fault.
ん？
私が➡
It's because I told him I wanted to stop the Holy Knights.
聖騎士を止めたいと言ったから➡
七つの大罪の所在を
探り出すために こんなむちゃを｡
In order to get information about the Seven Deadly Sins...
He's so reckless...
エリザベスちゃん…｡
ごめんなさい｡
Elizabeth...
I'm sorry.
Lord Meliodas, I hope you get better soon.
メリオダス様
早く よくなってくださいね｡
What should we do now?
さて どうしたもんかな｡
Let's wait until Lord Meliodas wakes up.
メリオダス様の目が覚めるのを
待ちましょう｡
We can think about the Baste after—
バステ監獄へは それから…｡
I'm going to the Baste Dungeon myself.
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)
バステ監獄には 僕一人で行く｡
I'm sure that heading to the Baste Dungeon is the first thing that Captain will do when he wakes up.
目が覚めたらさ 団長は➡
すぐバステ監獄に行くって
言うと思う｡➡
ケガが治りきってないのに
そんなことさせられない｡
Until he's fully healed,
I won't let that happen.
≫ガチャ
ディアンヌ様 私も お供します！
Lady Diane, I am coming as well!
Oh, please, you'll just slow me down.
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)足手まといは お断り｡➡
With that tiny body and those skinny arms...
そんな小さい体で
そんな細い腕でさ➡
What exactly do you think you can do?
一体 何ができるっていうわけ？
You may be a princess,
王女さんにできることなんて➡
せいぜい
団長のタオルを取り替えて➡
but all you can do now is be
Captain's nurse and change his linens.
看病するぐらいじゃないの？
What's up with your attitude?
そんな言い方あるかい！
世の中の女の子の大半は➡
Not every girl in the world is big and strong like you!
てめぇみたく
でかくて強いわけじゃねぇんだよ！
私も 何か
メリオダス様の力になりたいです｡
Even I...
want to be of some help to Lord Meliodas...
I don't want to be any more of a nuisance than I already am.
これ以上 迷惑をかけたくない｡
私のために もう
あんなむちゃをしてほしくは…｡
I don't want anyone to do
anything reckless for my sake—
あっ！
勘違いするな！
Don't get the wrong idea!
Captain isn't doing all this just for you!
団長は 君のために
むちゃしたんじゃない！
あっ｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)団長は 僕にだって…｡➡
Captain... helped me out, too...
昔から そういう男なんだからね｡
ディアンヌ様…｡
He's always been like that.
Lord Diane...
It was when I left my hometown and went traveling on my own.
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)
あれは 僕が ふるさとを出て➡
１人旅をしていたとき
つまらないことで➡
I got into some petty argument with a few knights...
どこかの騎士団と口論になって…｡
(回想)((ひぇ～！))
((き… 貴様！))
Y-You! How dare you!
((よくも やりおったな！))
((ふ～んだ！))
That's what you get for drawing your sword against such a beautiful girl.
((美少女に対して 男がそろって
剣を抜くのが悪いんだ～い！))
Like hell you're a beautiful girl!
(騎士)
((何が美少女だ！ 巨人族め))
Damn giants!
Go back to your homeland!
(騎士)((里に帰れ！))
(騎士)((お前らみたいな➡
There are no men or women for monsters like you!
化け物に 男も女もあるものか))
You make me sick.
((むかっ！ 人間なんて➡
You humans are so full of yourselves
just because there are so many of you!
数が多いだけの
ちっぽけな種族のくせに！))
Why, you...
((この～！ 言わせておけば))
((討ち取ってくれるわ！))
You think we're just gonna let you run your mouth?
Let's teach her a lesson!
((な… なんだ？ このガキ))
Who's this brat?
((我らを ｢金色の麦｣騎士団と
知っての行為か!?))
Do you understand that you're
fighting Knights of the Golden Wheats?!
((男が 寄ってたかって 女一人に
かっこ悪いことすんなよ))
You guys shouldn't act so high and mighty, ganging up on a girl like this.
((えっ…))
((貴様～！ 言い残すことは➡
Damn you!
Are those your last words?!
それだけか… うがっ！))
(騎士)((こっ この… むぎっ！))
R-Retreat!
(騎士)((た… 退却～！))
(騎士)((むぎぃ…))
((もう大丈夫だ))
Well, that's that!
((怖くなかったか？))
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)((えっ？))
Were you scared?
It was the first time in my life that someone asked me if I was scared.
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)｢怖くなかったか？｣
なんて言われたのは➡
生まれて初めてで｡➡
And it was to a girl much bigger than he was.
それも 自分より
こんなに大きい女にさ｡➡
今でも はっきり覚えてるんだ｡➡
I still remember it clearly, even now.
At the time, I felt like I'd become the
same height as the boy in front of me.
あのとき
自分が 目の前の男の子と➡
同じ身長になったように
錯覚したことを｡➡
もちろん分かってるよ そんなのは
錯覚にすぎないってことは｡➡
I understand, of course.
Those were just silly feelings.
I'm not small and cute like you, Little Princess.
僕は 王女さんのように
小さくも かわいくもない｡
I can't go inside a house,
so I can't even take care of Captain.
家にも入れないから
団長の看病だって➡
してあげられない｡
The only thing I can do is fight for him.
僕にできること
といえば➡
団長のために戦う
それぐらいだもん｡
That's it.
私は
聖騎士と戦う力が欲しいです｡
I want the strength to fight the Holy Knights.
大切な人たちを
この手で守る力が｡
I want to be able to protect those who are dear to me...
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)僕は 小さくなりたいよ…｡
I...
wish I were smaller.
Lady Diane...
ディアンヌ様…｡
あれは？
That's...
It's coming from the Baste Dungeon.
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)バステ監獄の方から来る｡
Are those... rain clouds?
雨雲でしょうか？
また あいつか？
Him again?
≪ブーーン…(虫の羽音)
ううん あの音は…｡
No... This is the sound of...
ブーーン…
まさか➡
This can't be...
Bugs?!
虫？
それも➡
Not just any bugs...
毒虫の大群だ～！
A whole swarm of poisonous ones!
(町人)うわぁ～！
(町人)なんだ これ!?
(町人)きゃあ～！
(町人)うわぁ～！
バステ監獄からの攻撃ですか!?
きゃあ！
Is this an attack from the Baste Dungeon?!
That means a Holy Knight is behind this!
ってことは 聖騎士の仕業か！
Diane, we're counting on you!
ディアンヌ ここは頼んだぜ！
きゃあ～！ 僕 虫 嫌～い！
I hate bugs!
(ｴﾘｻﾞﾍﾞｽ ﾎｰｸ)ええ～!?
Come, have a taste of my adorable insects' "Rain Capriccio"!
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)さあ
私の きゃわいいクソ虫どもの➡
雨の狂想曲を 味わいなさ～い！
Rain Capriccio
No way! At this rate, the whole town's gonna be annihilated!
やべぇ…
このままじゃ 町は全滅だぜ｡
あっ メリオダス様…｡
Lord Meliodas...
くっ！
あっ エリザベスちゃ～ん！
Elizabeth!
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)ドゥフフフ！ 町もろとも
溶かし尽くしちゃうのよ！
You're going to melt along with the whole town!
虫は嫌いだけど➡
I hate bugs, but...
団長のためなら なんでもないよ！
If it's for Captain's sake, I'll do anything!
これが ディアンヌ様の力｡
This is... Lord Diane's power?
毒虫全滅…｡ すげぇ～！
She destroyed 'em all! Amazing!
I'll crush every one of your insects!
ゴミ虫は
一匹残らず たたき潰す｡
I should say... As expected, right?
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)
さすが… と言うべきかしらね｡
Hey, teach me that move you just used—
おい
今の技 俺にも教え… プギ～！
団長のことは頼んだよ！
I'll leave Captain to you!
は… はい！
Y-Yes!
外で
あんだけ ドンパチやってたのに➡
He's sure resting comfortably despite all the racket outside.
のんきなもんだぜ｡
≫コン コン
How's the patient doing?
(ﾀﾞﾅ)患者の容体は どうですか？
おかげさまで➡
He's sleeping very deeply, thanks to your medicine.
先生の調合してくださったお薬で
ぐっすりです｡
It's almost like he's dead.
まるで
死んだみてぇに｡ プゴッ｡
Hawk! Don't say scary things like that!
ホークちゃん
怖いこと言わないで！
Well... Of course he is...
そう… でしょうね｡
(２人)あっ｡
Dr. Dana, thanks for your hard work.
≪ダナ君 ご苦労さま｡
首尾よく やってくれたようだね｡
You suitably held up your end of the deal.
あっ｡
プゴッ！
Wh-What was that?
な… なんだ!?
誰です!?
Who's there?
Wolfsbane, deadly nightshade, cantharidin and henbane's leaf.
トリカブト
ベラドンナ ミドリゲンセイ➡
A specially mixed deadly poison.
ヒヨスの葉を配合した劇毒を
飲ませました｡
This boy will never open his eyes again.
この少年は
二度と目覚めることはありません｡
あっ… 傷を癒やすための薬では
なかったのですか!?
It wasn't medicine for healing his wounds?
Even we wouldn't come out unscathed
in a battle against the legendary Seven.
≪いくら我々といえど
七つの大罪と➡
≪正面からぶつかれば
無事では済みませんからね｡➡
≪それに 王国は 目的を
果たすためなら 手段は問わぬと｡
Besides, for the kingdom to accomplish its goals, we have to take drastic measures.
誰なの!? 姿を現しなさい！
Who are you? Show yourself!
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)お初に お目にかかります｡
はっ！
Allow me to introduce myself.
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)我は ｢不気味な牙｣の一人
聖騎士ゴルギウス｡
I am the Holy Knight Golgius of the Weird Fangs.
Holy Knight...
聖騎士…｡
こいつ どっから？
Where'd he come from?
(ｺﾞﾙｷﾞｳｽ)エリザベス王女 御身を➡
Princess Elizabeth, I have come to pick you up.
お迎えに上がりました｡
We're going back and forth on a dead-end street, yo
itta ki tari de ikidomari yo
This abandoned dream is a bitter experience, yo
mihatenu yume wa kori gori kori gori yo
After all, this world we live in is transient, yo
shosen konoyo wa ukiyo no sekai
Open up and renew yourself to find high spirits, yo
hirakinaoreba NORINORINORINORI yo
High spirits, yo!
NORINORI yo
Throw in the firewood to reignite
maki wo kubero tayasu na sono hi wo
Your blazing passion before it goes out
tsuki ugokasu MONO wa sou kandou sa
The future will be fine as long as it shines brightly
mirai wa tada kagayaite kurete ireba ii’nda
We switched our intense rampage on
bokura wa Gan Gan abare MO-DO
Making seven sounds of thunder
todorokasu Boom Boom nanatsu no oto
Heading toward an ever-bright tomorrow
Rin Rin hikaru ashita e to susumou
We're ready to shoot the place up
bokura wa Bang Bang Haji ke MO-DO
Jumping here and there as we go
buttobasu Ran Dom SUTAIRU de ikou yo
Shining through like a diamond
Bling Bling hikaru DAIYAMONDO
iku ze Now we can fly high
Let's go, now we can fly high
(牢番)
なあ どっちが勝つか賭けねぇか？
Hey, wanna bet on who wins?
(牢番)ん？
(牢番)｢不気味な牙｣と➡
Between the Weird Fangs
and the Seven Deadly Sins!
七つの大罪
今 町で戦ってるだろ？
They're fighting in the town now, aren't they?
That's not even worth betting on.
(牢番)賭けになんねぇよ｡
七つの大罪って➡
The Seven Deadly Sins just have
their captain and one more, right?
団長と もう一人くらいしか
いないんだろ？➡
現役の聖騎士様４人に
かなうわけが…｡
They have no chance against the Weird Fangs—
Hey!
≪いいねぇ～！
(牢番)あっ…｡
That's pretty interesting.
≫それ 面白ぇわ｡
ガン！
(２人)あっ！
(牢番)ひぃ～！
(牢番)う… うそだろ…｡
N-No way!
ああ～ 久々の散歩はいいねぇ｡
It's nice to get out for a walk every now and then.
Fox's Sin of Greed, Ban, of the Seven!
(牢番)
七つの大罪 強欲の罪のバン！
<The Seven Deadly Sins>
The Fox's Sin of Greed
Ban
You...
(牢番)貴様 どうやって脱獄した!?
(牢番)なぜ 今？
How did you break out?!
Why now?
(ﾊﾞﾝ)見りゃ分かんだろ｡➡
You can tell just by looking.
蹴破ってだよ｡ んんっ！➡
I kicked the door down.
お前らがさ～
激面白そうな話 してたろうがぁ｡➡
It's because you guys were
having such an interesting chat.
生きてたんだって～？➡
He was alive?
Our cap'n...
うちの団ちょ｡
(２人)ひっ！
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)なんの騒ぎだ？
(牢番)おお～！
What's the commotion?
Lord Jericho!
(牢番)ジェリコ様！
Huh?
ああ？
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)七つの大罪のバンか｡➡
The Deadly Sin, Ban...
I don't know how you got out of your cell,
but you'd better go back in.
どうやって牢を出たのか
知らないが とっとと戻れ｡
Look here, brat.
おい ガキ｡ 英雄に対して➡
That's no way to speak to a hero, is it?
口の利き方が
なってないんじゃねぇの？
You dare address an apprentice Holy Knight as "brat," huh?
聖騎士見習いの俺を
ガキ呼ばわりか｡
For a half-dead criminal,
you sure like to run your mouth.
瀕死の大罪人が
口だけは達者なものだ｡➡
ゴルギウス様たちに
お伝えしろ｡➡
Send a message to Lord Golgius!
脱走し 抵抗を図った囚人を➡
A prisoner broke out of his cell and resisted,
so Lord Jericho had no choice but to kill him.
やむなく ジェリコが葬ったとな｡
(２人)はっ！
Yes, ma'am!
(ﾊﾞﾝ)ぐわぁ～～！➡
あっ あぁ… あぁ～あ～｡
切り過ぎちまったかなぁ？
Wonder if this is too short?
あっ！
(ﾊﾞﾝ)まあ さっぱりしたし➡
Well, it feels refreshing.
Guess it'll have to do.
よしとするかぁ｡
You've got talent, you know... as a hairdresser.
お前 才能あるぜ～ 散髪の｡
You dodged my blade despite
having wounds all over your body?
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)
その傷で 俺の剣をかわしただと!?
Wounds? What wounds?
傷？ どの傷だぁ？ ああ～？
バカな…｡ さっきまで➡
No way...
You just had steel stakes
hammered through your limbs.
四肢を 鋼の鉄杭で
打ちつけられていたはず｡
Remember this well, brat.
(ﾊﾞﾝ)よ～く覚えとけよ ガキ｡
あっ！
傷ってのはよぉ
こういうやつのことな？
This is what you call a wound, got it?
Though the wound he gave me... is what you'd call a special case.
やっぱ
あいつに付けられた傷だけは➡
特別製… だな｡
Next Episode's Report
The Weird Fangs order of the Holy Knights are here!
＜聖騎士フリージアが現れた！＞
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)ドゥフフフ！
来たわね 七つの大罪｡➡
You've finally come, Sins!
ここから先は 通さないわよ～｡
But you won't get past me!
＜エリザベスとディアンヌが
逃走した！＞
Elizabeth and Diane have escaped!
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)この私に
恐れをなして 逃げたようね｡
Looks like they ran away in fear of me.
いや お前の そのﾌｧｯｼｮﾝｾﾝｽに
ビビって逃げた｡
No, they ran away because of your fashion sense.
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)えっ!?
しかも その虫➡
And those bugs... You really need a bath.
お前 ちゃんと風呂入れよ｡
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)ち… 違う！
Y-You've got it wrong!
次回 『七つの大罪』
｢たとえあなたが死んでも｣｡
Next time on The Seven Deadly Sins: "Even if You Were to Die."
(ﾌﾘｰｼﾞｱ)
私はただ 自然を愛するだけの➡
I'm just a noble maiden who loves nature!
清き乙女なの！
Episode 5
Even if You Were to Die
I'm just a noble maiden who loves nature!
安倍総理大臣は自衛隊創設６０周
年の
航空観閲式で訓示し､
集団的自衛権の行使を可能にする